Guide to the Donald Clifford Gallup Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- April 2001 Acquisition, 1866-2000; 14; 78.5; (87 boxes) + 4 record album storage, 4 art, 1 object storage
  - Other Papers
    - Appointment calendars and diaries, 1971-1978; 6
    - Appointment calendars and diaries, 1979-1991; 16 (Box 82)
    - Appointment calendars and diaries, 1992-1997; 7 (Box 83)
    - Flowers of Friendship; advance proofs, 1953 August 17
    - Transcripts of Gertrude Stein correspondence
      - Anderson, Sherwood, undated; 3
      - Aswell, Edward, undated
      - Atlantic Monthly, undated
      - Buss, Kate, undated
      - Cerf, Bennett, undated
      - Coburn, Alvin Langdon, undated
      - Cone, Etta, undated
      - Cook, William, Mr. & Mrs., undated
      - Crowninshield, Frank, undated
      - Daniel, Ellen, undated
      - Goodspeed, Charles, undated
      - Gibb, Harry Phelan, undated
      - Haas, Robert Bartlett, undated
      - Hubbell, Lindley W., undated; 2
      - Keogh, Andrew, undated
      - Lynes, George Platt, undated
      - Maratier, George, undated
      - Maurer, Alfred, undated
      - McBride, Henry, undated
      - Pollock, Anna Marble, undated
      - Rogers, W. G., undated
      - Rosie, Francis, Sir, undated
      - Sears, undated; 2
      - Stein, Julian, undated (Box 84)
      - Stein, Rosellen, undated
      - Steward, Samuel, undated
      - Stieglitz, Alfred, undated
      - Thomson, Virgil, undated; 3
      - Weeks, Mabel Foote, undated
      - White, Max, undated
      - Whitehead, William, undated
      - Wilcox, Wendell, undated
      - Unsorted correspondence, undated; 15
    - Books and Pamphlets by or translated by Ezra Pound; typescript, undated (Box 85)
    - T. S. Eliot; a Bibliography; typescripts, undated; 6
    - Giuseppe Baretti's Work in England, 1939, undated; 3
      Includes notes, drafts, and final dissertation.
    - Giuseppe Baretti's Work in England; typescript, undated (Box 86)
    - Books and Pamphlets by Gertrude Stein; typescript, undated
    - Pound, Ezra. Plays Modelled On the Noh (1916); edited by Donald C. Gallup, 1986, undated; 2
      Includes notes, drafts, galley proofs, and author's final proof.
    - Bibliography & Ezra Pound, 1967, undated
    - "Book-Collecting and Bibliography", undated
    - Carter & Pollard, undated; 2
    - Rutgers, notes, undated
    - "Du côté de chez Stein", 1967, undated
    - Grolier Club talk, 1948?
    - "A Hodge-Podge of Oddities", undated; 2
    - "How Pleasant to Know Mr. Lear!", undated
    - Introducing Marianne Moore, undated
    - Letters from England, 1937
    - 42nd Annual Meeting of the College Art Association of America, Philadelphia, 1954
    - "Mr. Eliot at the Churchill Club", undated
    - Review, undated
    - Stein, Gertrude, 1944, undated; 3
    - Stieglitz, Alfred, undated
    - "The Ezra Pound Archive at Yale", undated; 4
    - Swampscott, 1948?
    - T. S. Eliot & Ezra Pound, undated; 4
    - T. S. Eliot & Ezra Pound, undated; 2 (Box 87)
    - "Taste, Technique & Utility in Book Collecting", undated
    - "The William Carlos Williams Collection", undated
    - Yale Club talk, undated
    - Pigeons on the Granite; reviews, 1988-1989, undated; 2
    - Bibliography, 1983 August
    - Bollingen Prize, 1965-1975, undated
    - The Dial Papers; notes & documents, 1986-1987, undated
    - Durrell, Lawrence, undated
    - Eliot, T. S.; first draft, 1947, undated
    - "The "Lost" Eliot Manuscripts", undated
    - "The Cocktail Party", undated
    - England, undated
    - Gaudier, undated
    - Hemingway, Ernest, undated
    - Hulme, Kathryn, undated
    - Lascaux, Élie, undated
    - Lear, Edward, undated
    - Luhan, undated
    - O'Neill, Carlotta, undated; 2
    - Pearson, Norman Holmes, undated
    - Pound, Ezra, undated
    - Rudge, Olga, undated
    - Sitwell, 1983 August
    - Southern Methodist University, undated
    - Toklas, Alice B., undated
    - Van Vechten, Carl, undated
    - Wilder, Thornton, undated
    - Wilson, Edmund, 1961-1965, undated
    - Wood, Mrs., undated
    - Yale, 1983
    - Zermatt Journal, undated
    - Eliot - "F. M.", undated
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1965-1994; 2
    - Material by or relating to Thornton Wilder
      - Collected Short Plays; edited by Donald Gallup, undated; 3
      - Collected Short Plays; edited by Donald Gallup, undated (Box 88)
      - Printed material, 1994-1998, undated; 3
      - Collected short plays project, 1994-1997, undated; 3
      - Manuscripts, undated
      - Notes on manuscripts at Yale, undated
      - Unsorted correspondence, 1976-1995, undated; 3
      - Permissions, etc., A - Z, 1976-1993, undated; 3
      - Harvard University Press, 1979
      - Harrison, Gilbert, circa 1978-1992
      - Brandt & Brandt, 1966-1988; 4
      - Brandt & Brandt, 1989-1993 (Box 89)
      - Harper & Row, 1976-1984; 3
      - Union Trust, 1966-1994; 5
      - Wiggin & Dana, 1979-1992
    - Material by or relating to Eugene O'Neill
      - Eugene O'Neill and His Eleven- Play Cycle, undated; 2
      - Rosie (plays piano), undated
      - Nietzsche, undated
      - Blemmie, undated
      - 1925, undated
      - Notes, undated
      - Appendix A: O'Neill's Ideas for Production, undated
      - Introduction, early draft, undated; 2 (Box 90)
      - Appendix B: O'Neill's Reading, undated
      - Notes on O'Neill's reading, undated
      - Library (at C. W. Post), undated
      - Chronology (from Work Diary), 1930-1951, undated; 10
      - "O'Neill's Plans For the Cycle", undated
      - "The Eugene O'Neill Collection at Yale", undated
      - Notebooks & cycle papers, undated; 3
      - Interviews: George Jean Nathan, undated
      - Interviews: Sergeant, E. S., undated
      - Sergeant, E. S., undated
      - Time, October 21, 1946, undated
      - Transcripts and photocopies of Eugene O'Neill correspondence, undated; 10
      - Notes from Carlotta's diaries, undated
      - IX. Nothing Is Lost But Honor; Golden Spike, clippings, 1969
      - I. O'Neill, undated
      - II. O'Neill, undated
      - VIII., early version, undated
      - Eugene O'Neill's Tale of Possessors Self-Dispossessed, 1996, undated; 7 (Box 91)
      - Notes, undated
    - Photocopies, transcripts, and publications of Thornton Wilder writings and correspondence
      - "The Acolyte", undated
      - "The Alcestiad", undated; 2
      - "And the Sea Shall Give Up Its Dead", undated
      - "Bernice", undated
      - "Cement Hands", undated
      - "A Christmas Interlude", undated
      - "Childhood", undated
      - "The Drunken Sisters", undated
      - "The Emporium", undated
      - "Flamingo Red", undated
      - "The Growth of the Bridge of San Luis Rey", undated
      - "In Praise of Guynemer", undated
      - "Infancy", 1961
      - Journal, undated; 6
      - Journal, undated; 3 (Box 92)
      - "The Long Christmas Dinner", undated
      - "The Last Miracle of the Graal", undated
      - Letters to Cheryl Crawford, photocopies, undated
      - Letters to Mario La Serna, photocopies, undated
      - "The Marriage We Deplore", undated
      - "The Melting Pot", undated
      - "Mr. Bozzy", undated
      - "Not for Leviathan", undated
      - "Our Century", undated
      - "St. Francis Lake", undated
      - "Selected Essays", undated
      - "Solvs Inter Deos Potens", undated
      - "Someone from Assissi", undated
      - "The Song of Maria Bentedos", undated
      - Stein, undated
      - "Theophilus in New York", undated
      - "The Unerring Instinct", undated
      - "The Wreck on the Five-Twenty-Five", undated
      - Youth, undated
      - Thornton Wilder Journals (1939-1961), 1985 August; 8
      - Thornton Wilder Journals (1939-1961), 1984 March 21; 9 (Box 93)
    - Eliot, T. S. Miscellaneous broadsides, etc., 1956, undated
    - Blurbs, 1964, undated
    - Unsorted correspondence, 1998-2000, undated; 2
    - O'Neill, Eugene. "The Calms of Capricorn", 1981
    - Wilder, Thornton. "The Skin Of Our Teeth"; French translation, undated
    - Exhibition catalogues, 1980, undated
    - Unsorted notes, undated
    - Pigeons on the Granite, 1988
    - Eliot, T. S. Inventions of the March Hare; edited by Christopher Ricks, undated
    - Blanck, Jacob, 1996-1997, undated (Box 94)
    - Permissions, 1996, undated
    - Printed ephemera and photographs, circa 1976-1994; 2
    - Publications by or relating to Gertrude Stein
      - Petits Poèmes, 1944
      - "Francis Rose," exhibition catalogue, undated
      - "Riba-rovira", 1945, undated
      - "Literally True", 1947
      - Gertrude Stein, 1947
      - Gallup collections, undated
      - "Last Will and Testament", 1974
      - "From a Play by Gertrude Stein", undated
      - "Capital Capitals", 1968
      - "Tender Buttons", 1934-1965
      - New Vistas in Song, 1964
      - Rorem, Ned. Three Sisters Who Are Not Sisters, 1974
      - Cone, Claribel, undated
      - Gallup, Donald. The Flowers of Friendship, 1953
      - "An Airborne Interview", 1999
      - "Etienne and Florence and Georges and their Mothers and French Social Station", 1999
    - "Robert Nathan", undated
    - Restrictions, undated
    - Stein / Toklas correspondence, undated
    - Stettheimer, Ettie, 1951-1952
    - Tchelitchew, Pavel, undated
    - What Mad Pursuits, undated; 2
    - Flowers of Friendship, undated
    - Élie Lascaux, undated
    - Unsorted notes, undated
    - Autobiography, undated
    - "John Carter", undated
    - "An Evening at Catherine Coffin's", undated
    - "The Cult of the Object", undated
    - Marinetti, undated
    - Notes and correspondence, 1990, undated
    - Nathan, Robert, undated (Box 95)
    - Lescaux, J. E., undated
    - Ficke, Gladys Brown, undated
    - "The Gaston Lachaise Archive", undated
    - Laughlin, James, undated
    - "Little Alice", undated
    - Kirstein, Lincoln, undated; 4
    - "Jonathan Edwards College", undated
    - Stein catalogues, 1970, undated; 2
    - What Mad Pursuits; typescript, undated
    - O'Neill, Eugene. Poems, undated
    - "The Calms of Capricorn", 1976
    - Notes and receipts, circa 1965-1981
    - Stein programs, circa 1969-1986; 3 (Box 96)
    - Stein. Translations. German, undated
    - Lescaux, early drafts, undated
    - "Henry McBride", undated
    - Miltzlaff, Max, undated
    - Persons, Places & Problems, undated
    - Jonathan Edwards College, undated
    - "Muriel Draper and Her Son Paul", undated; 3
    - Zermatt, undated
    - Hospital, undated
    - What Mad Pursuits, circa 1998-1999; 4
    - Photographs and negatives
      - Eliot, T. S., 1932-1936, undated; 2 (Box 97)
      - O'Neill, Carlotta, undated
      - Rudge, Olga, undated
      - Jackson, L. R., undated
      - Lear, Edward, undated
      - Lascaux, Élie, undated
      - Framed photograph of unidentified couple, undated
      - Stein, Gertrude, undated
    - Postcard Album, circa 1904-1908
    - Printed Material
      - Printed material relating to T. S. Eliot, circa 1980-1986
      - Publications of Donald C. Gallup
        - "Aldis, Foley, and the Collection of American Literature at Yale," The Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, Volume 42, 1948 (Box 98)
        - "Aldis Foley, and the Collection of American Literature at Yale," offprint, undated; 2
        - "The Altschul Collection: A Check-List," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 44, Number 2, 1969 October
        - "Always Gtrde Stein," Southwest Review, Volume 34, Number 3, 1949 Summer; 2
        - "Baretti's Reputation in England," offprint, undated
        - "Boobliography and Ezra Pound," Texas Quarterly, Volume 10, Number 4, 1967 Winter
        - "Boobliography and Ezra Pound," offprint, undated
        - "A Book is a Book is a Book," The New Colophon, Volume 1, Part 1, 1948
        - Book reviews for Dallas News, 1937-1946
        - Review of Brinnin, John Malcolm. The Third Rose, undated
        - "Carl Van Vechten," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 55, Number 2, 1980 October
        - "Carl Van Vechten's Gertrude Stein," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 27, Number 2, 1952 October
        - "The Carter and Pollard 'Enquiry' Fifty Years After," The papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, Volume 78, Number 4, 1984; 2
        - "The Carter and Pollard 'Enquiry' Fifty Years After," offprint, undated
        - A Catalogue of the Published and Unpublished Writings of Gertrude Stein, 1941
        - "Cataloguing and Handling Research Materials in the Large Collection," Proceedings of the Conference on Materials for Research in American Culture, 1956
        - "The Charles J. Rosenbloom Bequest: A Check-List," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 49, Number 4, 1975 April
        - "Collecting Edward Lear," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 61, Numbers 3-4, 1987 April
        - "The Collection of American Literature," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 48, Number 4, 1974 April
        - A Curator's Responsibilities, 1976 September
        - "Du côté de chez Stein," The Book Collector, Volume 19, Number 2, 1970 Summer (Box 99)
        - "Du côté de chez Stein," offprint, undated
        - "The Eliots, and the T. S. Eliot Collection at Harvard," offprint, undated
        - "The Eugene O'Neill Collection at Yale," The Eugene O'Neill Newsletter, Volume 9, Number 2, 1985 Summer-Fall
        - "Eugene O'Neill's 'The Ancient Mariner'," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 35, Number 2, 1960 October
        - "Exhibition of Writings by T. S. Eliot," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 11, Number 4, 1937 April
        - "Ezra Pound," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 50, Number 3, 1976 January
        - "Ezra Pound," offprint, undated
        - "Corrections and Additions to the Pound Bibliography," Paideuma, Volume 1, Number 1, 1972
        - "The Ezra Pound Archive at Yale," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 60, Number 3-4, 1986 April
        - "Ezra Pound's Experiment for Esquire," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 67, Numbers 1-2, 1992 October
        - "Ezra Pound's Experiment for Esquire," Paideuma, Volume 22, Numbers 1-2, 1993 Spring-Fall
        - "Ezra Pound's 'An Opening For Agamemnon'," Paideuma, Volume 15, Numbers 2-3, 1986, undated; 2
        - Review of Firmage, George J. "E. E. Cummings: A Bibliography," The Book Collector, Volume 9, Number 4, 1960 Winter
        - "A Letter From B. Franklin," published by Donald C. Gallup, 1936
        - "Gertrude Stein and the Atlantic ," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 28, Number 3, 1954 January
        - "The Gertrude Stein Collection," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 22, Number 2, 1947 October
        - Grolier Club - Exhibition, 1976
        - Review of Hofer, Philip. Edward Lear as a Landscape Draughtsman, undated
        - "Jared Eliot Association," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 21, Number 4, 1947 April
        - Review of Lepper, Gary M. A Bibliographical Introduction to Seventy-Five Modern American Authors, offprint, undated
        - "Letters of American Writers," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 35, Number 4, 1961 April
        - "The Manuscript of 'The Waste Land'," The Times Literary Supplement, 1968 September 7
        - "Introducing Gertrude Stein," The Widening Circle, Volume 1, Number 4, 1973 Fall
        - "The Lost Manuscripts of T. S. Eliot," Bulletin of the New York Public Library, Volume 72, 1968 December
        - "The Lost Manuscripts of T. S. Eliot," offprint, undated
        - "The Mabel Dodge Luhan Papers," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 37, Number 3, 1963 January
        - "The Making of The Making of Americans ", undated
        - "More Letters of American Writers," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 37, Number 1, 1962 July (Box 100)
        - "Mr. Eliot at the Churchill Club," The Southern Review, Volume 21, Number 4, 1985, undated; 2
        - Review of Noakes, Vivien. Edward Lear. The Yale Review, Volume 59, Number 2, 1970 Winter
        - Review of Froula, Christine. To Write Paradise. Paideuma, Volume 16, Number 3, 1987 Winter
        - "Hawthorne's "The Battle-Omen'," The New England Quarterly, 1936 December
        - "The Paul Leicester Ford Collection," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 30, Number 2, 1955 October
        - "Picasso, Gris, and Gertrude Stein," Picasso, Gris, Miro, exhibition catalogue, 1948
        - "Pigeons is People," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 63, Numbers 1-2, 1988 October
        - "The Pleasure of Their Company," offprint, undated
        - C.A. Stonehill, Inc. A Selection of Old and Rare Books, edited by Donald C. Gallup, 1939
        - "T. S. Eliot & Ezra Pound," The Atlantic Monthly, 1969
        - "T. S. Eliot and Ezra Pound: Collaborators in Letters," Poetry Australia, Number 32, 1970 February
        - "Taste, Technique, and Utility in Book Collecting," The University of Rochester Library Bulletin, Volume 38, 1985; 2
        - "Two Early Manuscripts of Sinclair Lewis," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 29, Number 1, 1954 July
        - "Two Old Letters," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 24, Number 1, 1949 July
        - "The Value, Disadvantages, and Use of Letters," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 28, Number 2, 1953 October
        - "The Weaving of a Pattern", 1948 November
        - "The William Carlos Williams Collection at Yale," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 56, Numbers 1-2, 1981 October
        - "The First Separately Published Atlas Entirely Devoted to the Americas," offprint, undated (Box 101)
        - "The Yale Collection of American Literature," The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 38, Number 4, 1964 April
        - T. S. Eliot & Ezra Pound, 1970
        - Introduction to Katherine Hulme's Of Chicken and Plums, 1982
        - "Elie Lascaux", 1951
        - A Catalogue of English and American First Editions of Writings by T. S. Eliot, compiled by Donald C. Gallup, 1937; 2
      - Serials and Magazines
        - The Antigonish Review, Number 90, 1992 Summer
        - Eugene O'Neill Foundation Newsletter, 1984-1999
        - The Eugene O'Neill Newsletter, 1981-1988; 3
        - The Eugene O'Neill Review, 1989-1997; 6
        - Harvard Library Bulletin, 1996-1997 (Box 102)
        - In the Works, 1995 Fall
        - James Joyce Quarterly, Volume 32, Numbers 3-4, 1995
        - The Library Chronicle, Volume 26, Numbers 1-2, 1995
        - The New Yorker, 1996-2000
        - Nota Bene, 1987-1998
        - The Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1948-1998; 2
        - The Southern Review, Volume 21, Number 4, 1985 Autumn
        - The Texas Quarterly, Volume 10, Number 4, 1967 Winter
        - T. S. Eliot Society Newsletter, 1997
        - Ukraina i Svit, Volume 22-23, 1961-1962
        - Vanity Fair, 1999 March
        - The Yale Review, Volume 78, Number, 1989 Winter
        - The Yale University Library Gazette, Volume 71, Numbers 3-4, 1997 April
      - Warren, Charles. T. S. Eliot on Shakespeare, 1985
      - T. S. Eliot: The Modernist in History; edited by Ronald Bush, 1991
      - Stead, C. K. Pound, Yeats, Eliot and the Modernist Movement, 1986
      - Lepenies, Wolf. Between Literature and Science, 1985 (Box 103)
      - Omnium Gatherum: Essays for Richard Ellmann, 1989
      - A Creative Century: Collections at the University of Texas, 1964
      - Gallup, Donald C. What Mad Pursuits!, 1998
      - Gertrude Stein, Picasso & Juan Gris, 1971
      - Prokosch, Frederic. Voices: A Memoir, 1983
      - Pizetti, I. Assassinio nella Cattedrale, 1958
        Includes music scores as well as libretto by T. S. Eliot in German and in Italian.
      - The Siege of Charleston / Action at Combahee Bluff, undated
      - Geographic Expeditions, 1999
      - Aurelius, Marcus. Am I My Brother's Keeper?, 1945
      - Farmer, David. Stanley Marcus: A Life With Books, 1993
      - Unsorted exhibition catalogues, small publications, and other printed ephemera, 1990s; 4
      - Unsorted exhibition catalogues, small publications, and other printed ephemera, 1990s; 3 (Box 104)
      - In and Out of Africa, 1995
      - An Obsession With Fortune, 1994
      - Dallas Museum of Art. The Year in Review, 1997-1998
      - Bookseller Catalogues
        - R. A. Gekosi, 1991, undated
        - Haskell House Publishers, Ltd., 1979
        - Bertram Rota, 1997
        - Joseph the Provider, 1995
        - Loblolly Books, 1996
        - Thomas A. Goldwasser Rare Books, 1991-1997; 2
        - William Reese Company, 1995-1999; 2
      - Unsorted articles by Donald C. Gallup, 3
      - Empty black binder entitled "Gallup. Pursuits. Volume 3", undated
    - Scrapbooks, 1949-1950 (Box 105)
    - Scrapbook, undated (Box 106)
    - Printed material relating to T. S. Eliot, circa 1920-1980 (Box 107)
    - What Mad Pursuits, undated
    - Music scores with lyrics by T. S. Eliot, circa 1951-1965; 3
  - Artwork
    - John, Augustus. "Philantropists," pen & wash drawing, undated (Box 108 (Art))
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia. "The House I Live In," oil on canvas, 1937 (Box 109 (Art))
    - Lascaux, Élie. "La Terrasse des Widka," oil on canvas, undated (Box 110 (Art))
    - Tunnard, John. "Sentinel," oil on canvas, undated (Box 111 (Art))
    - Bronze bust of T. S. Eliot on wooden base, undated (Box 112 (Art))
  - Restricted Fragile Material
    - "Osburn, Dodd. German Poems and Songs", undated; (1 10" record album) (Box 113 (Record Album Storage))
    - "Giorgio Tozzi, Bass-Baritone Sings Paul Reif, Five Songs to Poems by T. S. Eliot", undated; (1 7" 33 1/3 RPM record album)
    - "Speech From 'Murder in the Cathedral'", undated; (1 10" record album)
    - "Memorial Record of Homage to T.S. Eliot", 1965; (1 33 1/3 RPM record album) (Box 125 (Record Album Storage))
    - "Old Possum's Book of Practical Cats", circa 1957; (1 33 1/3 RPM record album)
    - "T.S. Eliot: Poesie Detta da Giorgio Albertazzi", circa 1960s; (1 33 1/3 RPM record album)
    - "T.S. Eliot Reading Poems and Choruses: Ash Wednesday, The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock and Others", circa 1955; (1 33 1/3 RPM record album)
    - "T.S. Eliot Reads His Four Quartets", circa 1940s; (1 33 1/3 RPM record album)
    - "T.S. Eliot Reads - Old Possum's Book of Practical Cats", circa 1957; (1 33 1/3 RPM record album)
    - "T.S. Eliot: The Waste Land and Other Poems", circa 1950s; (1 33 1/3 RPM record album)
    - "Thomas Stearns Eliot, Reading His Poems: Gerontion and The Hallow Men", circa 1934; (1 33 1/3 RPM record album) (Box 126 (Record Album Storage))
    - "Twentieth Century Poetry in English, An Album of Modern Poetry: An Anthology Read by the Poets", 1955; (3 33 1/3 RPM record albums)
    - "Twentieth Century Poetry in English, T.S. Eliot: Reading His Own Poems", 1946; (1 33 1/3 RPM record album)
    - "The Cocktail Party, by T.S. Eliot", 1950; (2 33 1/3 RPM record albums) (Box 127 (Record Album Storage))
    - "Twentieth Century Poetry in English, Contemporary Recording of the Poets Reading their Own Poems: T.S. Eliot", 1949; (5 33 1/3 RPM record albums)
    - "Excerpts from the music of Ezra Pound" (2001.ycal.0424-f.0001), undated; (1 CD-R) (Box 114)
    - "Robert Penn Warren - Birthday Salute!", undated; (1 audiocassette) (Box 115)
    - "Bernetta Quinn, O. S. F. Robert Warren Penn", undated; (1 audiocassette)
    - "Listen and Play It For Whom...", undated; (1 audiocassette)
- April 2001 Acquisition, 1754-1979; 15; 1.46; (2 boxes)
  The April 2001 Acquistion consists of writings of others, including typescripts of The Journals of Thornton Wilder, edited by Donald Gallup. Printed material contains chiefly bookseller catalogues. Correspondence consists of letters to and from Marianne Moore and James Cabell, as well as third-party correspondence by Djuna Barnes, Marsden Hartley, Lewis Wyndham, Virgil Thomson, and others acquired by Donald Gallup.